Yes.
It hurt my neck so I really thought that something had broken, so I didn't dare move.
The staff believed that too called 112, and then came an ambulance.
Ambulance could not get yourself up, then the fire brigade came.
It was totally crazy!
Four firefighters and two ambulance personnel lifted me up on a stretcher with a lot of Velcro, type.
We have got a lot of time on the day's question on Instagram about how you feel.
I went to the hospital and was x -rayed.
They saw that nothing was wrong, so I had to go home.
- So now we have a little ... what do you say?
Stucking dad.
- Yes.
- But you shouldn't be all day?
- No no.
Or, it's not really our car.
We have a collaboration with Mitsubishi who lends this pearl to us over the summer.
And I never want to return it.
We go on a road trip with this.
So it is a plug-in hybrid which means we can only take a cord ... into our electrical outlet.
Then we can drive for 4 miles and when the electricity runs out we drive on gasoline.
It's absolutely amazing, I'm in love with it.
Now that we live in the countryside we almost only drive on electricity.
It's absolutely fantastic!
It is great for nature.
- You should suck in here.
- Yes!
Now I stop!
- Now the inside of the car is clean.
- Yay!
Good job, everyone.
- And I found money on the ground!
SEK 5.
- How nice.
- You're rich.
- Yes, worst Lyllo.
Now we will drive a giant card and then we will wash the outside of the car.
If you wash the car then I can build a hut with you a little later.
- Yes!
- Kurrisin ...
- "Kurrisin" ... Kurrisin Frances comes over.
- Yes.